so my 10 and seven-year-old uh were that
age when we took them to Disney for the
first time and uh we took them to Disney
and SeaWorld for seven days and I refer
to these seven days like it were the
seven days I spent in
Vietnam I did seven days in the Orlando
Sun with Walt and Savannah and my wife
Ashley and I still have
flashbacks we stayed at Animal Kingdom
Lodge cuz I didn't want to ever have a
saving
account and I heard probably a thousand
times from my little 10-year-old and
seven-year-old so much garbage that I
said a million times W Savannah there
are other people staying in this hotel
that don't want to hear all that from
you and they're like but the ice cubes
are shaped like Goofy and the and the
chocolate is shaped like Mickey and
there's elephants that run through in
the morning I'm like walk so there are
other people staying in this hotel that
don't want to hear all that from you and
my 10-year-old Savannah's like Dad I
don't think they can hear us through the
hall your father is
right there are other people staying in
this hotel that don't want to hear all
that from
you so my 10-year-old Savannah is
awesome love her she's great I wouldn't
change your hair on her head but she is
a little Daredevil and she will ride
anything and uh I rode nothing as a
child and I ride nothing as an adult
mostly cuz I'm terrified of
heights and she was watching videos of
every roller coaster and found the Manta
roller coaster at SeaWorld and she
decided she was going to ride it and I
found videos of kids getting off the
ride crying and I was showing her those
videos and she watched the first one of
this like 13-year-old kid getting off of
it having a panic attack crying and
she's like let's
go so we're in line at the Manta and I'm
like Savannah
I want to let you know that Daddy didn't
really ride rides like this when I was a
kid nor do I ride them now but I'm going
to ride it with you but you might hear
me scream a really bad swear
word and I need you to not tell
Mom she's like it's all right Dad we
learned them all from the
neighbors so you got to
understand you're on the mant roller
coaster right you sit under it you're
under the track you sit in it like a ski
lift so your feet are down England and
then right as you Embark out on the
journey this is what
happens click so now you're not lying
under the track like a ski lift you're
on under the track like this and it
looks like it might have been
uncomfortable and it
was they say in the advertising you feel
like you're flying like Superman but no
not at all it's really more like you're
staple to the back back of a
bat flying straight into
Hades and then I'd go out on it and go
up the clicket clack clicke clack
clickity clack and I'm terrified of
height so all I over hear in the
clickity Clack is like you're going to
die you're going to die you're going to
die so I shut my eyes and I go all the
way to the top of my eyes shut and on a
normal roller coaster when you get to
the crest of the Hill you open your eyes
and you see all of God's creation you
see the Horizon you see the sun setting
you see the clouds you see your daughter
and you're like this is awesome
yay but on the Manta roller coaster
you're under the track so when you open
your eyes you're looking down into the
parking
lot where your head will be bludgeoned
when you
fall so you swoop down the roller
coaster like this facing this way and go
up and into an inverted Loop lying on
your back which is horribly confusing
and I thought we had flown off the track
and we're spinning off into the parking
lot so I'm just like oh swear
word
and Savannah is next to me like
this and I'm like oh she is having a
good
time and my life went into slow
motion I read this ride is 90
seconds surely I can survive 90
seconds oh only
89 more
seconds so only need one thing to do in
this moment and was only equipped to do
one thing in this moment so I did
it Our
Father who AR in heaven Hallowed be thy
name thy kingdom come th will be done on
Earth as it
[Music]
is forgive us our d as we for forgive
our debtors unless is trespasses Lord
I've never quite got the hang of that
one oh we're done we're done Savannah
that wasn't even that we're done that's
not done oh how do they do that in
gravity that's different technology I
don't understand I look in Savannah's
like
yay and I'm like yay that I walk through
the valley of the shadow of
death I will Fe heal it's surely
goodness love in the house of the Lord
forever oh we're done we're done we're
done Savannah jumps off the ride and is
like let's do it
again
no you are an
Abomination so we get off the ride we
get back to the hotel to the Animal
Kingdom Lodge and we're sleeping boy
girl cuz my 10-year-old girl won't sleep
with my seven-year-old boy and I'm like
why won't you sleep with Walt Savannah
and she said dad he's just always
[Laughter]
moist what does that even
mean and she said you'll
see so I'm in bed with Walt
wrapped around trying to not touch him
keeping like an 8 in buffer and steam is
rising from his
head like you know when you're on the
concrete and it's hot and you can't see
through it cuz it's like I couldn't even
see my wife from
the somewhere in the middle of the night
about 5:45 in the morning the trumpeting
sound of flatulence
enters the
hotel 60% of you were like oh that's
disgusting
and 30% of you were like no no no that's
hilarious and 10% of you were like
what's
flatulence but it jolts Walt out of bed
like R out of a bugle in the Marine
Corps just
like and he flips over a few times and
lands on his feet like a cat and he's
like
Dad there are other
people staying in this hot
[Music]
your boy is
right there are other
people oh you guys are
great Disney
World